stg.do 2017-12-29

# Staged - Social Engagement Marketing

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which STAGED MEDIA INC. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.staged.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by STAGED.

### PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked, as appropriate, to verify their email address.

Users may, however, visit parts of our Site anonymously.

We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

### NON-PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### WEB BROWSER COOKIES

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### HOW WE USE COLLECTED INFORMATION

STAGED collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes: 

  1. To improve customer service 
    * Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  2. To personalize user experience. 
    * We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  3. To improve our Site. 
    * We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  4. To process transactions. 
    * We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  5. To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature.
  6. To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  7. To send periodic emails.

The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

### HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

STAGED has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### CONTACT DETAILS

In the event that the user needs to contact STAGED for purposes related to these terms and conditions, the following contact details may be used:

STAGED Media Inc.  
278 Anderton Rd.  
Comox, British Columbia   
Canada  
Web: www.staged.com  
E-Mail: support@staged.com
